Guide to the Refuse & Resist! Records TAM.362
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I. National Office, 1986-2008; 20.50 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 25 manuscript boxes, 3 oversize flat boxes, 1 small flat box, 1 cassette box, 3 flat-file folders, and multiple items and files within 3 shared boxes in various sizes; 1 websites in 1 archived website; 44 audiocassettes; 
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- NPR Censorship, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Organizing Material Pre-1995, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Play, May 1995 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0063)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Press Clippings, 1992-1995 (Box 37, Folder 9, Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Protests at the Democratic and Republican Conventions, 2000, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Resource Book on the Case of Mumia Abu-Jamal, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Shaka Sankofa Research, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Tribunal Program Planning, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Working Group, 1996-1997, 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Workshops and Strategy Session Planning, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Writings by C. Clark Kissinger, 1996-2001 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Writings by Mumia Abu-Jamal, 1990-1994 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Writings by Mumia Abu-Jamal, Blu Magazine, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Music Censorship Material, 1987-1992 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - National Conference, May-June 6-7, 1987
    - Press Conference Conclusion Audio Recording, May 19, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0022)
    - Schedules, Promotional Material, Planning Files, June 6-7, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 5-8, Box 25, Folder 1, Box 38)
    - "Ramboism", Part One-Two Audio Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0025)
    - "Ramboism", Part Three Audio Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0026)
    - "Gearing up the Mechanisms of Repression and Mass Detention" Video Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0069)
    - "Gearing up the Mechanisms for Repression and Mass Detention" Video Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0055)
    - "The Reactionary Offensive Against Women" Video Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 41, Vhs 362.0079)
    - Resist Racism Workshop Audio Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0028)
    - Resist Racism Workshop Video Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0053)
    - Secular Humanism Workshop Audio Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0029)
    - "God Save Secular Humanism" Audio Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0030)
    - "Arts and Culture" Audio Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0032)
    - "Resurgent Racism" Audio Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0033)
    - "Resurgent Repression of Women in America" Video Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0049)
    - "AIDS and Strategies for Social Control", Part One Video Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0050)
    - Closing Plenary Audio Recording, June 6, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0031)
    - "Nazi Germany", Part One Video Recording, June 7, 1987 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0076)
    - "Nazi Germany" Audio Recording, June 7, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0034)
    - "War On Drugs" Audio Recording, June 7, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0035)
    - Drug Workshop Audio Recording, June 7, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0027)
    - "Speak English: The Assault on Immigrants" Workshop Video Recording, June 7, 1987 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0054)
    - "Speak English: The Assault on Immigrants" Workshop Video Recording, June 7, 1987 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0056)
    - Last Plenary, Part One-Two Audio Recording, June 7, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0037)
    - Last Plenary, Part Three-Four Audio Recording, June 7, 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0036)
    - Women's Workshop, Part One-Two Audio Recording, circa June 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0023)
    - Women's Workshop, Part Three-Four Audio Recording, circa June 1987 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0024)
  - National Conference Repression Workshop Speech, circa 1987-1989 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - National Conference, July 27-29, 1989
    - Schedules, Promotional Material, Planning Files, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - "Drugs & Foreign Policy", Part One Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0006)
    - "Drugs & Foreign Policy", Part Two Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0004)
    - "How the War On Drugs Comes Down", Part One Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0010)
    - "How the War On Drugs Comes Down", Part Two Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0011)
    - "Other Countries' Drug Problems", Part One Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0014)
    - "Other Countries' Drug Problems", Part Two Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0015)
    - "Police In the Drug Trade", Part One Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0012)
    - "Police In the Drug Trade", Part Two Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0013)
    - "Positive Alternative To Drug War", Part One Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0016)
    - "Positive Alternative To Drug War", Part Two Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0017)
    - "Racism and the War On Drugs", Part One Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0005)
    - "Racism and the War On Drugs", Part Two Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0009)
    - "Treatment/Prevention-1st Casualties", Part One Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0007)
    - "Treatment/Prevention-1st Casualties", Part Two Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0008)
    - "The War On Drugs and the Law", Part One Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0020)
    - "The War On Drugs and the Law", Part Two Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0021)
    - "What Must Be Done To Win", Part One Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0018)
    - "What Must Be Done To Win", Part Two Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0019)
    - "What's Behind the War On Drugs?", Part One Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0001)
    - "What's Behind the War On Drugs?", Part Two Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0002)
    - "Woman & War On Drugs" Audio Recording, July 27-29, 1989 (Box 42, Audiocassette 362.0003)
  - National Conference -- Resist '96, 1995-1996
    - Promotional Material, Schedules, Planning Files, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 4-10, Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Opening Plenary Video Recording, April 26, 1996 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0051)
    - Continued Video Recording, April 26, 1996 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0060)
    - Plenary, Part One Video Recording, April 26, 1996 (Box 41, U-matic 362.0087)
    - Plenary, Part Two Video Recording, April 26, 1996 (Box 41, U-matic 362.0084)
    - "Police State" Video Recording, April 26-28, 1996 (Box Shared Tamiment 086, Hi8 362.0040)
    - "Litigation" Video Recording, April 26-28, 1996 (Box Shared Tamiment 086, Hi8 362.0039)
    - "White Women Black Men" Video Recording, April 26-28, 1996 (Box Shared Tamiment 086, Hi8 362.0038)
    - Awards, Part One Video Recording, April 26-28, 1996 (Box 41, U-matic 362.0083)
    - Awards, Part Two Video Recording, April 26-28, 1996 (Box 41, U-matic 362.0085)
    - Closing Plenary Video Recording, April 28, 1996 (Box Shared Tamiment 086, Hi8 362.0041)
    - Opening Plenary Video Recording, April 26, 1996 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0061)
    - Continued Video Recording, April 26, 1996 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0062)
    - Resist '96 Video Recording, April 26-28, 1996 (Box 41, U-matic 362.0086)
    - Continued Video Recording, April 26-28, 1996 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0052)
  - National Conference Recordings, circa 1987-1996
    - Plenary, Tape One Video Recording, circa 1987-1996 (Box 41, U-matic 362.0089)
    - Plenary, Tape Two Video Recording, circa 1987-1996 (Box 41, U-matic 362.0088)
    - "Secular Humanism", Part One Video Recording, circa 1987-1996 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0071)
    - "Secular Humanism", Part Two and "War On Drugs", Part One Video Recording, circa 1987-1996 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0072)
    - "War On Drugs", Part Two Video Recording, circa 1987-1996 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0075)
  - National Council Meetings, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 11-13)
  - National Council Meetings, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 14-17)
  - National Council Meetings, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - National Council Meetings -- General Information, Communications, 1989-1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - National Council Meetings, 1990-1996 (Box 26, Folder 4-21, Box 27, Folder 1-3)
  - National Council Meetings, 1997-2002, undated (Box 27, Folder 4-16)
  - National Speaking Tour -- Draft Outline, Fliers, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Office Meetings, Notes, Related, 2000-2002 (Box 27, Folder 18-19)
  - Office Rules, Staff Agreement, Notes, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Partner Organizations -- Anti-Racists Action, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Partner Organizations -- Not in Our Name Project, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 3, Box 43)
  - Partner Organizations -- October 22 Organization / Stolen Lives Project, 1996-2001
    - Paper Files (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_362_ER_1
  - Poems, 1987-2002 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - "Politically Correct", 1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Press Clippings, 1989-2003 (Box 28, Folder 7, Box Shared Tamiment 164, Folder 23)
  - Press and Media Contact Lists, 1996-2000 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Press Packet, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Projected Budget for Fiscal Year 2000, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Public Service Announcement Campaign, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Public Service Announcements, October 22, 1996 (Box 40, Vhs 362.0067)
  - Public Service Announcements -- Chicago and San Diego, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 086, Audiocassette 362.0046)
  - Publications -- Counterattack, 1987-2001 (Box 29, Folder 1-4, Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Publications -- Refuse & Resist!, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Publications -- Refuse & Resist! Notes, 2000-2002 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Radio Program -- We Won't Go Back Notes, Fact Sheets, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Announcements, Fliers, Mailers, Posters, 1989-2001 (Box 29, Folder 8-9, Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Counteroffensive Newsletter, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Fight Back Network, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Funding Applications, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Mailing Lists, 1995-2001 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Men Support Reproductive Rights, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Meeting Notes and Correspondence, 1995-2000 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- National Day of Appreciation for Abortion Providers, 1996-2004 (Box 30, Folder 6-9, Box 31, Folder 1-8, Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- National Day of Appreciation for Abortion Providers, undated (Box 40, Vhs 362.0068)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Operation Rescue Protests, 1988-1998, undated
    - Promotional Material, Notes, 1988-1998 (Box 31, Folder 9-10, Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Tape One Video Recording, undated (Box 40, Vhs 362.0073)
    - Tape Two Video Recording, undated (Box 40, Vhs 362.0074)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Pensacola Protest, May 8, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Photographs of Protests, 1992, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Press Clippings, 1990-1998 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Rally in Wichita, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Roe vs. Wade 25th Anniversary Events, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Shut Down the Court Demonstration, 1989-1991 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Sticker, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Art Print by Sue Coe Used as Poster, circa 1992 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- T-shirt (partial section) "Gag Me with a Hanger", undated (Box 39)
  - Reproductive Freedom Task Force -- Ten Point Program Fliers, circa 1990-2001 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Resist in Concert! -- Announcements, Statements of Support, Planning Advisory Board, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 6-8)
  - Resist in Concert! -- C. Clark Kissinger Letters, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Resist in Concert! -- Organization Contact List, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Resist in Concert! -- Poster, 1988 (Flat-file-folder Temp 1)
  - Resist in Concert! -- Press Clipping, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Resist in Concert! -- Notes, Planning, Musician Idea List, Venues, Budget, 1988, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1-5)
  - Resist in Concert! -- Artist Files, Participants, 1988, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 6-8)
  - Resist in Concert! -- Artist Files, Non-Participants, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
  - Resist in Concert! -- Correspondence, Committees, Promotional Material, Planning, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 3-6, Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Resist in Concert! -- Contacts, Advisory Board, Sponsor and Organizer Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 7-9, Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- 3rd Bass, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Augustin, Jimmy and Atkinson, Connie, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Allen, Woody, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Anderson, Laurie, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Atkins, Robert, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- B-52s, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- B.A.D., 1988 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Ballinger, Lee, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Belatini, Alisa, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Biafra, Jello, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Black Rock Coalition, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Bloom, Howard, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Bragg, Billy, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Calamar, Gary, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Carlin, George, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Catino, Jean, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Chin, Brian, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Christagau, Robert, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Clinton, George, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Colichman, Paul, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Conal, Robbie, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Connolly, Emmett and Perry, Hart, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Cook, Jeff, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Cosgrove, Stuart, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Cucci, Nick, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- D., Chuck, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Davis, Miles, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Delsener, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Dewhurst, Colleen, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Eldred, Bill, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- First World Inc., 1988 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Fishbone, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Fourratt, Jim, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Gabriel, Juan, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Giuccione, Jr., Bob, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Goldberg, Danny, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Goldwait, Bob, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Grass, Randall, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Grateful Dead, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Greene, Joanne, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Haber, Bobby, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Haring, Keith, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Hendryx, Nona, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Ice-T, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Kampo Cultural Center, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Kelly, Karen and Laureiro, Anne, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Kline, Brad, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Kravitz, Lenny, 1988-1991 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Kristofferson, Kris, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Lasalle, Chris, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Latifah, Queen, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Le Guin, Ursula, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Levy, Joe, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Licher, Bruce, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Liebe, Tim, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Lindsay, Clinton, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Living Color, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Marder, Jonathan, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Margolis, Dave, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Marsh, Dave, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- MC Lyte, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- McCarthy, Bill, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Midnight Oil, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Nelson, Jeffrey, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- O'Connor, Sinéad, 1988-1991 (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Osborne, Jeff, circa 1988 (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Patterson, Rob, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 68)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Pearl, Ed, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 69)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Plotkin, Joe, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Powers, Stephen, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 71)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Rathe, Steve, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 72)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Roulston, Kathy, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 73)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Rowland, Mark, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 74)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Sachs, Robert, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 75)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Sanchez, Ricardo, 1987-1990 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Sanchez, Sonia, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Sarandon, Susan, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Scher, John, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Schwartz, Debbie, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Scott, Gerald, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Seeger, Pete, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Shepherd, Stephanie, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Shinehead, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Shock, Elaine, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Smith, RJ, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Starr, Victoria, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Stewart, Gary, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Tate, Greg, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Thau, Marty, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Uterberger, Richie, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Wali, Merisah, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- WBAI DJs, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Wexler, Haskell, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Williamson, Chris, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Resist in Concert! Notes / Correspondence -- Young, Jeff, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Resurgent America -- Book-related, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Sinéad Brigade Material, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Susan B Anthony Award Nomination Material, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Talking Points for Refuse & Resist! Program, April 2003 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Teachers' Network, undated (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Update on All Parts of the Organization, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Various Refuse & Resist! Issue Fliers, Handouts, Press Releases, Article Reprints, Protest Posters, 1989-2003 (Box 36, Folder 28, Flat-file-folder Temp 2, Flat-file-folder Temp 3)
  - War on Drugs -- Brochures, Fliers, Statements, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Website -- Archived Website, March 28, 2014
    The organization officially dissolved in 2006 and the website ceased updating in 2008. The website contains news listings, their CounterAttack newsletter, and their artists network. The website was active from 2002-2008.
  - Website Backup Files, 1996, 2000
    - July 6, 1996, TW_TAM_362_ER_2
    - December 29, 1996, TW_TAM_362_ER_3
    - July 8, 2000, TW_TAM_362_ER_4
  - Website -- Committee Reports, Notes, Meetings, 1998-2001 (Box 36, Folder 30-31)
  - Workshop Proposal -- "Women in the Global Economy", 2001 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Series II. Chapters, 1987-2001; 3.68 Linear Feet in 6 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize flat box, 1 small flat box